{
    "subject": "resource/Scoop_(2006_film)",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Scoop",
    "human_readable": "The name of the movie Scoop (2006 film) is Scoop.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9778698682785034,
            "question": "Is there a movie called Scoop that came out in 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9665283560752869,
            "question": "Which film was released in 2006 and called 'Scoop'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9505693316459656,
            "question": "Is the name of the movie 'Scoop'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9016709327697754,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie featuring the title 'Scoop'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8298425078392029,
            "question": "What title does the movie Scoop have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7728700637817383,
            "question": "Name a movie from 2006."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6788862347602844,
            "question": "What year was the movie Scoop released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6238166093826294,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie released in 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5762293934822083,
            "question": "When did the movie Scoop come out?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3942188322544098,
            "question": "What is the movie titled?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of the movie Scoop (2006 film) is Scoop.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8273_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did the movie Scoop come out?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8273_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the movie released in 2006?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8273_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the movie Scoop released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8273_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8273_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"Scoop\" is a 2006 American-British romantic comedy crime film, but they also mention another film called \"Scoop\" released in 2019, which has received lukewarm reviews. Therefore, the information does not support the triple that the movie \"Scoop\" (2006 film) has the name \"Scoop\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are already at least four other movies out there called Scoop.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}